Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Records MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV. Financial Material, 1982-2017; 15.8 Linear Feet in 11 record cartons and 11 manuscript boxes.; 147 kilobytes in 6 files.
  - Check stubs, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Deep Dish TV directory sales, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Deep Dish TV income, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Ledger of expenses, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Orders - PTTV West, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Phone invoices, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Tax exempt status form, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Budget, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Budget - Deep Dish TV, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Check stubs, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Chemical Bank - statements, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Deep Dish TV - finances, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Grants, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Ledger of receipts and disbursments, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Orders complete, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 56-58)
  - Paper Tiger / Deep Dish distribution list, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Petty cash, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 2-4)
  - Receipts, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Receipts paid, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - Budget, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Budget - Deep Dish TV, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Check stubs, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Deep Dish TV finances, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Grants, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Ledgers, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Ledger of disbursment, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Check stubs, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Complete orders, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 19-21)
  - Grants, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Grants - Benton Foundation, FIVF, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Grants - Puffin Foundation, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Grant report, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Loan agreements, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Orders - PTTV West, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Budget, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Check stubs, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Complete orders, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 32-34)
  - Grants, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Grant report, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Andy Warhol Foundation, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Mid-Atlantic Visual Arts, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - NYCCRM - franchise negotiations, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Orders - PTTV West, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Rental invoice - electronics, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Bills, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Bills - TCN, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Bills - UPS (for GCTV), 1991 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fed-Ex receipts, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Financial report, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Grants, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Ledger book - GCTV, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Tape sales / rentals, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Bills, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Bills - TCN, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Budget, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Grants, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Grants - Art Matters Inc., 1992 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Grants - DCA, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Grants - NAMAC, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Grants - NEA, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Grants - The New York Community Trust, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Grants - NY Foundation for the Arts, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - International sales, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Invoices, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Receipts - shipping, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Bills, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Bills - TCN, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Budget, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Grants, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Grants - Manhattan Neighborhood Network, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Grants - NAMAC, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Grants - NEA, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Invoices, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Invoices - tape sales, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Receipts, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Bills, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Bills - TCN, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Budget, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Donations, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Grants, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Grants -- DeeDee Halleck, 1994; FA_MSS_276_ER_22
  - Grants - NAMAC, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Grants - NEA, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Grants - NEH Media Alliance, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Grants - NY Council on the Humanities, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Paul Robeson Fund, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Invoices, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Invoices - tape sales, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Orders - PTTV West, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Receipts - shipping, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Budget -- Deep Dish TV, 1994-1995; FA_MSS_276_ER_20
  - Biils, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Distribution, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
  - Grants, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Grants - DCA, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Grants - Funding Exchange emergency grant info, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Insurance, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Insurance - old, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Invoices, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 21-22)
  - Invoices - Signal to Noise, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Invoices - tape sales, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Receipts - shipping, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Sales - Refunds and credits, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Taxes, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Bills, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Budget, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Expenses -- Deep Dish TV, 1996; FA_MSS_276_ER_21
  - Grants - DCA, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 1996
    - Electronic records, FA_MSS_276_ER_23
    - Paper materials (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Insurance, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - International sales, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Invoices, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Invoices - Media Alliance, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Receipts, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Amalgamated Bank - check stubs, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Bills, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Bills - NYNEX / Bell Atlantic, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Budget, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Complete invoice, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Grant - DCA, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Grant - Paul Robeson Fund / Funding Exchange, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Grant - MNN Revolving, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Grant - NYFA Community Assets, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Insurance, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - International sales, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Invoices, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Invoices - TCN, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Invoices - Wallace's Bookstore, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Receipts, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Record of Borrowing and invoices, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - USPS - 3602N form, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - A.J. Muste - Fiscal sponsorship, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Amalgamated Bank - check stubs, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Bills, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Bills - NYNEX / Bell Atlantic, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Budget - Northstar workshop, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Certificate of incorporation, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Charity registration forms, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Complete invoice, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 7-10)
  - Expenses, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Financial material, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Grants, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Grants - DCA, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Grants - North Star Fund, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Grants - Paul Robeson Fund, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Insurance, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Invoices, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Invoices - TCN, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Member reimbursements, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Receipts, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Volunteer Lawyers for the Arts, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Winnie Tam and Co. - PTTV financial info, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Accountant file, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Accountant's review report, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Bank reconciliations, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Bills - Bell Atlantic, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Bills paid, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 28-29)
  - Bills - TCN, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Book keeping, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Complete invoices, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 32, Box 23, Folder 1-3)
  - Donations, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Financial statement, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Grants, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Albert A. List Foundation, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Grants - List Foundation grant agreement, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Grants - MacArthur, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Grants - Open Society Institute, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Insurance, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Invoice - orders, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Member reimbursements, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Petty cash, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Receipts, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Winnie Tam and Co. - "Ask Winnie", 1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Winnie Tam and Co. - services proposed, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Accounting, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Bank reconciliations, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Bills - Citibank, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Bills paid, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 22-23)
  - Bills - TCN, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Budget, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Check stubs, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Citibank - charges by category, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Citibank - credit increase, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Citibank - quarterly reports, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Credit info for PTTV, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Expenses, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 31-33)
  - Financial Reports, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Grants, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Grants - MacArthur agreement, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Grants - MNN, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Grants - North Star application, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Grants - NYFA, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Open Society Institute, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Insurance, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Invoice file - Freedom Archives, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Invoices - tape orders, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Receipts, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Reciepts - miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Receipts - petty cash, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Reimbursement - Pacific Film Archive, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Video Rental Contracts, 2000-2014 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Audit, 2001; FA_MSS_276_ER_19
  - Budget - Treasury, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Check stubs, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Citibank - annual account summary, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Citibank - quarterly account summary, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Endorsment - Access Orbit, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Expenses, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Expenses - Sept-Dec, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Finances, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Financial Reports, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Fenced Out - distribution, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Grants, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Grants - DCA, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Grants - Experimental Television Center, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Grants - general overview, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Grants - MCAF agreements, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Grants - MNN reports and agreements, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Grants - North Star, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Grants - NYCH, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Grants - NYFA, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 30-31)
  - Grants - Resist application, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Invoices, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 33-34)
  - Invoices - tape sales, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Invoices - tape orders, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Payroll reports, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 37, Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Receipts - car rental, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Receipts - Citibank, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Reimbursement - Lightwork, Access Orbit, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Tax returns, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Winnie Tam and Co. - Annual report, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Winnie Tam and Co - audit, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Bills, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Citibank - business card expenses, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Expenses, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 10 - 11)
  - Financial reports, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 13, Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising - Queeruption, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Grants, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Grants - A.J. Muste, 9/11 Emergency Funds, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Grants -- Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Funding Exchange, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Grants - MNN application, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Grants - MNN, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Grants -- New York Community Trust, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 19, Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Grants - North Star, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Grants - North Star application, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Grants -- Robert Sterling Clark Foundation, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Winnie Tam and Co - financial materials, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Winnie Tam and Co - Mid-year financial report, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Grants -- Paul Robeson Fund for Independent Media, 2002-2007 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Grants -- North Star Fund, 2002-2008 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Citibank - quarterly report, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Citibank - statements, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Donors, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Expenses, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 27-28, Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Financial reports, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Financial statements, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Grants, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Grants - DCA, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Grants -- Funding Exchange, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Grants - MNN, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Grants -- National Endowment for the Arts, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 33-34, Box 26, Folder 1, Box 89)
  - Grants -- NYU Community Fund, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Grants -- Paul D. Shurgot Foundation, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Grants -- Rooftop Films Filmmakers' Fund, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Invoices - tape requests, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Invoices - tape sales and workshops, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Sales - tapes, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Grants -- Women's Film Preservation Fund, 2003-2004 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Video Distribution Reports and Sales Invoices, 2003-2009 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Grants -- Experimental Television Center, 2003-2010 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Bank Statements, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Deposits, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 9-11)
  - Expenses, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Financial Reports, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Grants, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Grants -- Ford Foundation, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Funding Exchange Emergency Grant, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Grants -- International Debate Education Association, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Grants -- Media Justice Fund, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Grants - North Star Fund, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Invoices - tape sales and workshops, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Sales - tapes, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 9-11)
  - Accountant Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Individual Donors, 2004-2013 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Bank Statements, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Bills - UPS, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Deposits, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 1-2)
  - Expenses, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 3-4)
  - Financial Consultation with Martha Wallner, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Financial Reports, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Grants, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Grants -- The Cricket Island Foundation, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Grants -- Nathan Cummings Foundation, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Grants -- Surdna Foundation, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Grants -- Threshold Foundation, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Invoices - tape sales and workshops, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Tax statements, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Bank Statements, 2005-2006 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Grants -- Manhattan Neighborhood Network, 2005-2008 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Budget Reports, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Deposits, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 3-4)
  - Expenses, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 5-6)
  - Grants - ADCO Counter Recruitment Fund, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Grants -- Citizens for NYC, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Grants -- Community Traning and Assistance Center, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Grants -- Grassroots Exchange Fund, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Grants -- Hyde and Watson Foundation, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Grants -- Ludwig Family Foundation, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Grants -- The New York Foundation, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Grants -- Norman Foundation, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Grants -- North Star Fund, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Grants -- Open Meadows Foundation, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Grants -- Open Society Institute, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Grants -- Progressive Technology Project, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Grants -- Sparkplug Foundation, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Grants -- Taproot Foundation, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Grants -- The Wallace Foundation, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Invoices - tape sales and workshops, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Grants -- Warhol Foundation, 2006-2007 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Bank Statements, 2007 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Deposits, 2007 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Distribution log, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Expenses, 2007 (Box 93, Folder 12-13)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2007 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Grants -- National Television Preservation Foundation, 2007 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2007 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Bank Statements, 2008 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Deposits, 2008 (Box 94, Folder 2-3)
  - Employee timesheets and receipts, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Expenses, 2008 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Financial Reports, 2008 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2008 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Grants -- National Cristina Foundation, 2008 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Bank Statements, 2009 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Deposits, 2009 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Expenses, 2009 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2009 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2009 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Bank Statements, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Deposits, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Expenses, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Bank Statements, 2011 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Deposits, 2011 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Expenses, 2011 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2011 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Grants -- A. J. Muste Memorial Institute, 2011-2016 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Bank Statements, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Deposits, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 8-9)
  - Expenses, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 10-11)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2012 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Bank Statements, 2013 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Deposits, 2013 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Expenses, 2013 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2013 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Bank Statements, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Deposits, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Expenses, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Grants -- Department of Cultural Affairs, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Budget Reports, 2014-2015 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Bank Statements, 2015 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Deposits, 2015 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Expenses, 2015 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2015 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2016 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Grants -- NYSCA, 2017 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Andy Warhol Foundation - guidelines, Undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Distribution info, Undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Grants, Undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Grants -- Third Wave Foundation, undated (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Invoices - tapes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Notes and fragments, Undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Receipts, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Inactive Funders, Various (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Restricted Financial Material, 1983-1999 (Box 27)
  - Restricted Financial Material, 2000-2004 (Box 28)
- Series V. Posters and Maps, 1968-2001; 2.7 Linear Feet in 12 oversize folders and 3 flat boxes.
  Series V. Posters and Maps (1968-2001) contains posters and maps that were collected by Paper Tiger TV and used for its productions and installations.
  Series V. Posters and Maps (1968-2001) is arranged alphabetically.
  - Anti-War demonstration poster and press release, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - "Bands Against Bush" poster, Undated (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Beaufortain - Olympics maps, Undated (Folder 29)
  - Bookmobile Project - poster / flyer, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Boycott of Salvadoran Coffee - "Kaos", Undated (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Certs - subway ad / poster, Undated (Folder 19 Right)
  - Defense Committee against Fascism - poster, Undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - "Diary of a Shirtwaist Striker" poster, Undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - European Media Arts Festival / University TV poster, Undated (Folder 25)
  - "Ewa: My Grandmothers Story" poster, Undated (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Institute for Democratic Socialism - poster, 1980 (Folder 20 Right)
  - Iran Contra posters, Undated (Folder 26)
  - "It's Possible" - Palestinian and Israeli art exhibit poster, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Map of New York, Undated (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Map of the forty primary trade areas, 1980 (Folder 21 Right)
  - Map of the World and the U.S., Undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Maps of New York, NY, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Media Mogul Tour signs by Mike Eisenmenger and Linda Ianannacone, 1998 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - "Nuclear Winter: Changing our Way of Thinking" poster, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - "Stop Bush's War in the Middle East" poster, c. 1991 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - "The Talking Band in Work-Song" poster, Undated (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Tats Cru - calendar, 2000 (Folder 22 Right)
  - University Gallery - "In the Shadow of..." poster, 1985 (Folder 28)
  - U.S. President fact wheel, c. 1980 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Van Gogh TV poster, 1991 (Folder 24)
  - "Vote the Big Bombs Out of the Big Apple" poster, Undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - "Women Get AIDS Too" [subway poster], Undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - World map - from FedEx, Undated (Folder 23)
- Series VI. Photographs, 1981-2001; 5.35 Linear Feet in 22 box binders, 2 flat boxes, and 1 manuscript box.
  Series VI. Photographs (1981-2001) contains photographs from the production of Paper Tiger TV's programming, installations, events, workshops, parties, and snapshots of the office and members.
  - Subseries VI.A: Show Stills, 1981-2001
    Subseries VI.A Show Stills (1981-2001) contains still images from Paper Tiger TV's television programs.